 {
    "PymultipleChoice" :[
        {
        "type" : "multiple-choice",
        "question" : "What do you use to create a function in Python?",
        "choice1" : "func",
        "choice2" : "function",
        "choice3" : "def",
        "choice4" : "void",
        "answer": 3
         
        },
        {
         "type" : "multiple-choice",
        "question" : "What is the term for creating a list in python?",
        "choice1" : "list",
        "choice2" : "array",
        "choice3" : "def",
        "choice4" : "function",
        "answer": 2
        }, 
        {
            "type" : "multiple-choice",
           "question" : "Who created python?",
           "choice1" : "Guido Van Rossum",
           "choice2" : "LeBron James",
           "choice3" : "Bill Gates",
           "choice4" : "Steve Harvey",
           "answer": 1
        }, 
        {
        "type" : "multiple-choice",
        "question" : "How do you print something in Python?",
        "choice1" : "print('Hello World')",
        "choice2" : "p('Hello World')",
        "choice3" : "def('Hello World')",
        "choice4" : "func('Hello World')",
        "answer": 1
        }, 
        {
        "type" : "multiple-choice",
        "question" : "Python is named after a...",
        "choice1" : "British Comedy Group",
        "choice2" : "Movie",
        "choice3" : "Snake",
        "choice4" : "Rat",
        "answer": 1 
        }
    ],

    "PyfillInBlank": [
        {
        "type" : "fill-in-blank",
        "question" : "A _____ is used to store values in python",
        "choice1" : "print('Hello World')",
        "choice2" : "def",
        "choice3" : "value",
        "choice4" : "array",
        "answer": 3 
        
    },
    {
        "type" : "fill-in-blank",
        "question" : "A ______ is used to store blocks of code",
        "choice1" : "print('Hello World')",
        "choice2" : "function",
        "choice3" : "lunch box",
        "choice4" : "def", 
        "answer": 2
        
    },

    {
        "type" : "fill-in-blank",
        "question" : "_____ is a programming language",
        "choice1" : "python",
        "choice2" : "cobra",
        "choice3" : "spider-man",
        "choice4" : "Michael Jordan",
        "answer": 1
        
    },
    {
        "type" : "fill-in-blank",
        "question" : "A ______ hold true or false value",
        "choice1" : "int",
        "choice2" : "string",
        "choice3" : "boolean",
        "choice4" : "double",
        "answer": 3
            
    },
    {
        "type" : "fill-in-blank",
        "question" : "A ______ is what is used to comment out code",
        "choice1" : "//",
        "choice2" : "<!-- -->",
        "choice3" : "$",
        "choice4" : "#",
        "answer": 4
    }
],
"PyTruenFalse" :
[
    {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "Python is a general purpose language",
        "choice1": "true",
        "choice2": "false",
        "answer": 1

    },
    {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "Python is a strongly type language",
        "choice1": "true",
        "choice2": "false",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "Python is a strongly type language",
        "choice1": "true",
        "choice2": "false",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "Python is a great language",
        "choice1": "true",
        "choice2": "false",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "0 is the first number in the index",
        "choice1": "true",
        "choice2": "false",
        "answer": 2
    }
],
"PyShort-Answer":
[
    {
        "type": "short-answer",
        "question": "Python files end with ____",
        "choice1": "py",
        "choice2": "java",
        "choice3": "json",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "type": "short-answer",
        "question": "a ____ loop, loops through an array",
        "choice1": "for",
        "choice2": "if",
        "choice3": "json",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "type": "short-answer",
        "question": "Central Processing Unit abbreviated is (_____)",
        "choice1": "JAV",
        "choice2": "WIFI",
        "choice3": "CPU",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "type": "short-answer",
        "question": "Big ____ Notation",
        "choice1": "S",
        "choice2": "O",
        "choice3": "J",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "type": "short-answer",
        "question": "You use a ____ drive to store extra data",
        "choice1": "USB",
        "choice2": "JSON",
        "choice3": "PY",
        "answer": 1
    }
]
}
